name: 'Past Simple: be'
questions:
  -
    question: 'We $ at home last night.'
    answers:
      - 'wasn''t'
      - 'didn''t were'
      - 'weren''t'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: "A: Where $ you last night?\nB: I $ at work all evening."
    answers:
      - 'was; was'
      - 'were; were'
      - 'were; was'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'A: $ she in the movies?\nB: No, she $.'
    answers:
      - 'was; was'
      - 'was; wasn''t'
      - 'were; weren''t'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'A: $ the movie good?\nB: Yes, it $'
    answers:
      - 'was; was'
      - 'was; wasn''t'
      - 'were; was'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ at work until 8pm today.'
    answers:
      - were
      - 'weren''t'
      - was
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'A: Were you in Orlando yesterday?\nB: No, we $. We $ in Miami.'
    answers:
      - 'wasn''t; was'
      - 'were; weren''t'
      - 'weren''t; were'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ a teacher?'
    answers:
      - 'Was she'
      - 'Were she'
      - 'She was'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'My brother $ in Rio last week.'
    answers:
      - were
      - was
      - is
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'We $ late yesterday.'
    answers:
      - are
      - were
      - was
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ a teacher, I $ a translator.'
    answers:
      - 'weren''t; were'
      - 'wasn''t; were'
      - 'wasn''t; was'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ at school yesterday?'
    answers:
      - 'was you'
      - 'you were'
      - 'were you'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'A: $ it a good book?\nB: Yes, it $.'
    answers:
      - 'Was; is'
      - 'Was; was'
      - 'Were; was'
    correct: 2
